Michael Nos

Phone: 603-854-3290 | Email: mnos9897@gmail.com | Manchester, NH

GitHub: https://mmnos.github.io/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-nos/

SUMMARY

A Full Stack Web Developer with a background in customer service and educated through the University of New Hampshire Coding Bootcamp. Through developed skills in Angular, React and MongoDB, I'm able to create an intuitive user experience through responsive web designs. I enjoy collaborating and problem solving to resolve user issues. Excited to leverage skills gained through previous work experience and projects towards creating responsive, effective websites.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5 - CSS - JavaScript - jQuery - Node.js - MySQL - MongoDB - Express - React - Angular

PROJECTS

Foodsta | https://github.com/mmnos/Foodsta | https://deliciousfoodsta.com/home

Full Stack

- Allows users to search for nearby restaurants, cuisines and meals
- Users can create accounts and post reviews about their meals
- Reviews are entirely crowd sourced and is based on specific meals rather than the restaurant itself
- Tools used: Angular, HTML5/SCSS, AWS S3, Auth0, Express, Sequelize, Node.js, Google Places API

Bay Calendars | https://github.com/emcoraccio/Project2 | https://secure-taiga-47401.herokuapp.com/

Full Stack

- Allows users to create accounts and safely stores their information inside the database using user authentication
- Once logged in, users can view their calendars and can schedule and request events
- Users are allowed to invite each other. If an invite is accepted, it will populate on their calendar with event details
- Tools used: Materialize, ¡Query, Node, Sequelize, Express, Passport, Handlebars, Moment

Moodify | https://github.com/mmnos/moodify | https://mmnos.github.io/moodify/

Front End

- App will suggest music based on the current weather, time of day and the mood set
- Responsibilities included gathering information from API's to display on the page and the overall design of the site
- Tools used: Materialize, jQuery, Moment.js, Spotify/OpenWeatherMap API

EMPLOYMENT

Target - Inbound Team Member - Bedford, NH

April 2019 - October 2019

- Assisted team members when necessary with stocking new merchandise and organization.
- Helped guests locate products and resolve other issues.

MegaFoods - Packaging - Manchester, NH

January 2019 - April 2019

- Ensured the correct product was being used for current task
- Confirmed current items met safety guidelines such as expiration dates and maintained cleanliness in the work space.
- Assisted in the upkeep of the product inventory.

EDUCATION

Coding Bootcamp Certificate: University of New Hampshire

June 2019 - December 2019

- A 24-week intensive technical program focused on developing skills in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express and React